Paul Dukas: Correspondence with Paul Poujaud
Yale University Music Library
- Letters from Poujaud to Dukas, Series II
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Paris, 1922 March 21; 1 page
    - Paris, 1922 June 05; 6 pages
    - Paris, 1922 July 05; 8 pages
    - Paris, 1923 July 12; 4 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Paris, 1925 May 22; 1 page
    - Paris, 1925 June 05; 4 pages
    - Paris, 1925 June 25; 4 pages
    - Paris, 1926 June 01; 1 page
    - Paris, 1926 July 31; 1 page
    - Valette, 1926 July 31; 4 pages
    - Valette, 1926 August 25; 4 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Valette, 1927 August 02; 8 pages
    - Paris, 1927 December 04; 2 pages
    - Paris, 1927 December 29; 1 page
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Guéret, 1928 August 25; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1928 September 17; 4 pages
    - Paris, 192S October 23; 1 page
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Paris, 1929 February 18; 2 pages
    - Paris, 1929 March 31; 2 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 April 06; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 April 27; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 May 22; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 June 03; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 June 10; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 July 13; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 August 12; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 August 28; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 September 20; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 October 30; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 November 21; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1929 December 30; 8 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Guéret, 1930 March 04; 8 pages
      Autograph letter signedr envelope
    - Guéret, 1930 April 01; 6 pages
    - Guéret, 1930 May 12; 6 pages
      Autograph letter signedI envelope
    - Guéret, 1930 July 19; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1930 October 01; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1930 December 30; 12 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Guéret, 1931 May 06; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1931 June 21; 3 pages
    - Guéret, 1931 July 06; 4 pages
    - Paris, 1931 August 31; 1 page
    - Guéret, 1931 September 18; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1931 October 23; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1931 December 10; 8 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Guéret, 1932 August 02; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1932 October 12; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1932 November 28; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1932 December 24; 8 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Guéret, 1933 April 25; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1933 June 26; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1933 July 24; 4 pages
    - Guéret, 1933 October 10; 8 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Guéret, 1934 January 20; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1934 May 07; 10 pages
    - Valette, 1934 September 02; 8 pages
    - Guéret, 1934 December 17; 4 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Guéret, 1935 January 29; 6 pages
    - Guéret, 1935 April 23; 8 pages
  - Letters from Poujaud to Dukas (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - 19?? ??, 1 page
    - Sunday, 1 page
    - Portrait of C. Franck, 1 page
- Letters from others, Series III
  - Letters from others (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Théâtre des Champs-Elysées, 1913 April 18; 1 page
      Typed letter signed
    - 1928 September 11, 1 page
    - 1934 ??, 1 page
      Autograph letter signed, photo
- Miscellaneous items, Series IV
  - Photographs of Paul Dukas, 3 items (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Métronome Enregistreur de Léon Roques. Paris: A. Durand., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 55)